Next, I will introduce the specific usage and attention to the sewing line type by this case.
You can notice that the curve before the front and the cap is too smooth, and the general hat has an obvious angle.
The simulation can be noticed that the version of sewing with the cap is not stable at the moment.
Conflicts like this are mostly caused by the sewing line type.
Since this part is two pieces of paper, it should be used to turn, and then the sewing line type will be modified to turn, and then the simulation will be stable.
If you want the front and the cap to have an obvious angle change, you can choose the sewing line type, and then modify its folding angle.
The number is greater than 180 when folding inward.
It will accompany whether the drawing is forward coordinate,vertical,or horizontal.
The same pattern will only be incorporated when we change to the second piece of fabric.
It will come off naturally.
If you place second piece of fabric like the iron piece inside the brown body, and regret it,we can go the wrong ways.
Right-ide cut to open the folding and the same piece fly down or turn, and potato will come out as a showed invarius from the other board per scene.
Although this is about the sewing line type, we manage to build the volume by述-ises earlier, which is aboutMIревwaveだけ,
So that it can be easily recognize the height of the fabric.
Next, we will go with the same method.
When we are done with the sewing line type, the main pattern larger than the size of the fold
We use a如此press line type, which will open a little, is a complex pattern.
After opening the surface mode in the濃密紋理, you can see that the gap is filled and there is an obvious layer relationship.
This is the thickness of the fabric. The reason why the conflict thickness of the panel and the thickness of the fabric overlap is because their sewing line type is called Turned.
The size of the gap between them, in addition to being affected by the thickness of the conflict between the panel and the panel, is also affected by the thickness of the fabric.
After reducing the thickness of the fabric, we can notice that the gap between the panel and the panel has become smaller.
The panel lining on the internal line is called Turned and cannot be modified to Custom Angle.
The panel lining is called Custom Angle and must be manually changed to Turned.
Here for example you see that I'm sewing with the Shoei
Time- stranded